revolutions2040.com 2017-12-23

# PRIVACY POLICY & DISCLAIMER - REVOS.2040

## _DISCLAIMER_

###### _The content on REVOS.2040  is information based on the opinions and scholarship of the authors. This site is intended for educational, motivational and commentary purposes only, both of which are strictly protected by Free Speech. The REVOS.2040 is not responsible for the opinions or content written by its writers. The information on this website is not intended to replace your relationship with a qualified health care professional and is not intended as final advice in any field, whether medical or otherwise. All trademarks and registered trademarks mentioned here are the property of their respective owners and are not used here for commercial purposes. _

###### _Paid advertising on REVOS.2040  may not represent the views and opinions of this website and its contributors. No endorsement of products and services advertised is either expressed or implied. _

###### _All the pictures and information shown on this blog are the property of their respective owners. We don’t hold any copyright about these pictures and news. We are not responsible for any incorrect or incomplete information. These pictures have been collected from different public sources including different websites, blogs considering to be in public domain. If any one has any objection to displaying of any picture and news, it may be brought to our notice by sending message through ‘contact us’ page & the same will be removed immediately, after verification of the claim. Contact us: **[Click Here. ](http://www.revolutions2040.com/contact-us/)**_

###### _Amazon affiliate disclosure:  REVOS.2040 is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com. By using the affiliate links, you are helping support the revolutions2040.com website_

## _PRIVACY POLICY_

###### _Nothing is more important to the owners and staff of REVOS.2040  than the protection of our users privacy. This notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used._

###### _**The Information We Collect**_

###### _This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Websites. On some  pages, you can specify personal profiles that may be viewable by other registered members of the Website. However, at no time do we collect your personal information such as name, address, or phone number, and we only require a functioning e-mail address for membership which will never be made publicly available. At no time do we attempt to reconcile any information you provide (including your IP address as indicated below) with offline identity or other personal information._

###### _Your e-mail address is not used for any additional purpose other than registration  for the Website and/or email newsletter and will never be shared with outside parties and is not viewable by unregistered members._

###### _The non-identifying aggregate information is not stored on any server owned by the  Websites as we do not collect or store any log files of activity on our websites._

###### _Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online  in ways unrelated to the ones described above. Your profile information is protected from web-spiders that search for e-mail addresses and other personal information. We reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable information associated with your account and/or posting history as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a court order or legal process served on REVOS.2040._

### _**Cookies**_

###### _From time to time data cookies will be set. At no time is any personally identifying  information (other than website username) ever stored in these cookies. The cookies are used to provide our application with page-to-page awareness of your user status and/or access privileges. Most of these cookies expire within days, but some may expire in months or years._
